Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/huynh-hieunguyen-440468124 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Strategy
Strategic Project Management
PMD

Languages

English

Huynh Hieu Nguyen

Group Project Manager

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Summary

Project Manager with over 9 years-experience in project, design and cost management

Proven ability to work in complex environment, to coordinate Multitasks in order to deliver projects within deadlines and budget. Highly organized and dedicated, energetic team player, reliable with a high sense of responsibilities, able to strategies and prioritize effectively to accomplish multiple tasks and stay calm under pressure, with emphasis on improving organizational consistency and adapt to changes

A committed professional of the PMD who enjoys learning new skills and undertaking challenges

Experience

Ash

1 year 5 months

Group Project Manager May 2024 - Present (11 months)

Ho Chi Minh City, Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Country Project Manager November 2023 - Present (1 year 5 months)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Au Chau Fashion And Cosmetic Co., Ltd (ACFC)
Deputy Project Manager
March 2023 - November 2023 (9 months)
Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

NOVALAND Project Manager April 2021 - March 2023 (2 years)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

ADP Architects
Project Manager
May 2020 - April 2021 (1 year)
Quân 1, Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Au Chau Fashion And Cosmetic Co., Ltd (ACFC)
Project Lead
June 2018 - May 2020 (2 years)
Vietnam

Playpoint Viet
Project Supervisor
July 2015 - June 2018 (3 years)
Vietnam

Project Supervisor
PLAYPOINT VIETNAM
(https://playpoint.asia)

Responsibilities

- Collect inquiries/ requests from clients, and propose 2D&3D design for children playground;
- Liaise with design team in Singapore for 2D&3D design proposal and support the team with 2D&3D design when needed;
- Calculate EPDM rubber floor quantity for import based on playground area & client's approved design;
- Liaise with oversea logistics team for product shipping schedule to update clients the delivery time;
- Have meeting with developers, main contractors, subcontractors to update implement of installation and solve arising problems (if any);
- Follow up with Project Manager/ Site Manager for site progress and adjust delivery & installation schedule if needed;
- Check goods at warehouse & arrange local transportation to deliver goods to sites;
- Site visit and ensure the site correct with the design;
- Direct and supervise project team regarding with installation ensuring appliance of company operational procedures;
- Direct and supervise project team regarding with installation ensuring appliance of company operational procedures;

- Ensure project team compliance with all applicable fire & life safety codes, building codes, environmental regulations, and other policies as requested by developers & government.
- Arrange transportation & manage payment for local delivery
- Prepare and ensure timely submission of appropriate paperwork such as: Construction Daily Record, Minutes of Inspection & Acceptance of Work Item, and other relevant documents;
- Manage maintenance budgets, project budgets to ensure that operations and projects are cost effective, completed in a timely and accurate manner, and are on budget;

Key project Reference:

- Estella Height 2 District 2
- Vivo City District 7
- AIS School, SISS School, BVIS School.
- Tao Dan Park
- Novaland project.

Education

University of Transport in Ho Chi Minh City
Bachelor of Engineering (B.Eng.), Traffic Planning · (2010 - 2015)